{
  "ent": [
    {
      "question": "zzzz ",
      "Answer": "zzzz",
      "option1": "zzzz",
      "option2": "zzz",
      "option3": "zzzz",
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "li ",
      "Answer": "li",
      "option1": "li",
      "option2": "li",
      "option3": "li",
      "id": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "entr",
      "Answer": "entr",
      "option1": "entr",
      "option2": "entr",
      "option3": "entr",
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "gggg",
      "Answer": "ggg",
      "option1": "gggg",
      "option2": "ggg",
      "option3": "gggg",
      "id": 5
    },
    {
      "question": "saSasasaASas",
      "Answer": "saSAsA",
      "option1": "SAsaSA",
      "option2": "sASasa",
      "option3": "saSSA",
      "id": 6
    },
    {
      "question": "jjjj",
      "Answer": "jjjj",
      "option1": "kkkk",
      "option2": "llllll",
      "option3": "mmmm",
      "id": 7
    }
  ],
  "lit": [
    {
      "question": "atoz",
      "Answer": "Cristiano Ronaldo",
      "option1": "Airana Grande",
      "option2": "Kylie Jenner",
      "option3": "Lionel Messi",
      "weight": 1,
      "id": "asfd"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following indian has won the oscar? ",
      "Answer": "Satyajit Ray",
      "option1": "Priyadarshan",
      "option2": "Yash Chopra",
      "option3": "Anurag Kashyap",
      "weight": 1,
      "id": "asfrr"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is the highest grossing movie in india?",
      "Answer": "Avengers:Endgame",
      "option1": "Avengers:Infinity War",
      "option2": "The Jungle Book",
      "option3": "FF8",
      "weight": 1,
      "id": "asff"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following indian actor has shared sliver screen with tom cruise?",
      "Answer": "Anil Kapoor",
      "option1": "Akshay Kumar",
      "option2": "Anupam Kher",
      "option3": "Irrfan Khan",
      "weight": 1,
      "id": "asfpi"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following movie was released in theaters?",
      "Answer": "Ramprasad ki tehrvi",
      "option1": "Gulabo Sitabo",
      "option2": "Laxmi bomb",
      "option3": "Ludo",
      "weight": 1,
      "id": "asfdiuy"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following indian has won the oscar? ",
      "Answer": "Satyajit Ray",
      "option1": "Priyadarshan",
      "option2": "Yash Chopra",
      "option3": "Anurag Kashyap",
      "weight": 1,
      "id": "asfdd"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is the highest grossing movie in india?",
      "Answer": "Avengers:Endgame",
      "option1": "Avengers:Infinity War",
      "option2": "The Jungle Book",
      "option3": "FF8",
      "weight": 1,
      "id": "astsd"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following indian actor has shared sliver screen with tom cruise?",
      "Answer": "Anil Kapoor",
      "option1": "Akshay Kumar",
      "option2": "Anupam Kher",
      "option3": "Irrfan Khan",
      "weight": 1,
      "id": "asfadds"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following movie was released in theaters?",
      "Answer": "Ramprasad ki tehrvi",
      "option1": "Gulabo Sitabo",
      "option2": "Laxmi bomb",
      "option3": "Ludo",
      "weight": 1,
      "id": "asjug"
    },
    {
      "question": "ooo ",
      "Answer": "ppp",
      "option1": "oooo",
      "option2": "oo",
      "option3": "ooo",
      "id": "T_dAKwN"
    },
    {
      "question": "vvvv",
      "Answer": "vvvv",
      "option1": "vvvv",
      "option2": "vvvv",
      "option3": "vvvvv",
      "id": "WuVxLdY"
    },
    {
      "question": "rrrr",
      "Answer": "rrrr",
      "option1": "rrrrr",
      "option2": "rrrrr",
      "option3": "rrrr",
      "id": "g6_Ym_m"
    },
    {
      "question": "xxxx",
      "Answer": "xxxx",
      "option1": "xxx",
      "option2": "xxxx",
      "option3": "xxxx",
      "id": "D5JNEMh"
    }
  ],
  "subject_data": [
    {
      "username": "abcd",
      "subject_name": "lit",
      "highest_score": "23",
      "no_of_times_attempted": "3",
      "total_ques": 12,
      "max_marks": 12,
      "id": 1
    },
    {
      "username": "abcd",
      "subject_name": "ent",
      "highest_score": "23",
      "no_of_times_attempted": "3",
      "total_ques": 12,
      "max_marks": 12,
      "id": 1
    },
    {
      "username": "abcd",
      "subject_name": "sports",
      "highest_score": "23",
      "no_of_times_attempted": "3",
      "total_ques": 12,
      "max_marks": 12,
      "id": 1
    },
    {
      "username": "abcd",
      "subject_name": "gk",
      "highest_score": "23",
      "no_of_times_attempted": "3",
      "total_ques": 12,
      "max_marks": 12,
      "id": 1
    },
    {
      "username": "abcd",
      "subject_name": "comp",
      "highest_score": "23",
      "no_of_times_attempted": "3",
      "total_ques": 12,
      "max_marks": 12,
      "id": 1
    }
  ],
  "users": [
    {
      "username": "Ghanshyam",
      "email": "sdfs@ew.dffd",
      "password": "d32c78b4596a6b63a5bf73708a15ac3f",
      "ent": "-1",
      "lit": "-1",
      "gk": "-1",
      "tech": "-1",
      "sports": "-1",
      "id": 12
    },
    {
      "username": "brk",
      "email": "dff@dss.dsf",
      "password": "6df5982a1b9512461368a1ad1df9159d",
      "ent": "-1",
      "lit": "-1",
      "gk": "-1",
      "tech": "-1",
      "sports": "-1",
      "id": 13
    },
    {
      "username": "abcd",
      "email": "dsf@das.ds",
      "password": "5975c85e8d2756810491f99edfa1cfed",
      "ent": "-1",
      "lit": "-1",
      "gk": "-1",
      "tech": "-1",
      "sports": "-1",
      "id": 14
    },
    {
      "username": "defg",
      "email": "fd@e.sfdf",
      "password": "f1ce609eb6591ecd3dc405282fef22f9",
      "ent": "-1",
      "lit": "-1",
      "gk": "-1",
      "tech": "-1",
      "sports": "-1",
      "id": 15
    },
    {
      "username": "g6",
      "email": "yddd@dfghjvhj.f",
      "password": "c9a140d1a756e793ea9a6927c070b6c7",
      "ent": "-1",
      "lit": "-1",
      "gk": "-1",
      "tech": "-1",
      "sports": "-1",
      "id": 16
    },
    {
      "username": "equinox",
      "email": "sdfd@fsd.ddf",
      "password": "b09767a1fc751ed53bf3f9bfe63894b2",
      "ent": "-1",
      "lit": "-1",
      "gk": "-1",
      "tech": "-1",
      "sports": "-1",
      "id": 17
    },
    {
      "username": "admin_1",
      "email": "sdfd@fsd.ddf",
      "password": "6df5982a1b9512461368a1ad1df9159d",
      "ent": "-1",
      "lit": "-1",
      "gk": "-1",
      "tech": "-1",
      "sports": "-1",
      "id": 18
    }
  ]
}